<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LIL</string>
    <string name="more_info">More info   >></string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="go">Go</string>
    <string name="zoom">Zoom in</string>
    <string name="zoomout">Zoom out</string>
    <string name="maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="list">List</string>
    <string name="spots">Spots</string>
    <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="intro">Intro</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="intro_title">Introduction</string>
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="intro_content">There are still a great many roads, squares and monuments in Liège which bear witness to a 19th century where the spirit of the entrepreneur and innovator were high on the agenda. To learn about these places through the words and ideas of Victor Hugo is the aim of the tour we’d like to take you on.
\n\n
The great Romantic writer, the author of Les Misérables and Notre-Dame de Paris, first passed through Liège in 1840 en route for Germany. In the course of his brief stay, he noted down his impressions and provided various bits of information – which were sometimes wrong – on the places he’d visited. These texts appear in The Rhine, published in English in 1848.
\n\n
We can suppose that, when he next came to Liège, in 1864, Victor Hugo saw profound changes in the urban landscape. At that time, indeed, the city was undergoing a complete transformation (“Liège is one of the cities in process of transition from old to new”); it was abandoning its medieval face to move forwards into modernity, a trend which doesn’t seem to have been too much to the author’s liking.
\n\n
All quotations are taken from: Hugo, V. “The Rhine”. New York: Wiley, J., 1848.</string>
    <string name="about_content">Year 2011 doesn’t celebrate Victor Hugo’s birth (1802) nor the anniversary of his death (1885) but the completion in 1861, in Mont-Saint-Jean (Waterloo), of his famous book Les Misérables.
\n\n
“Liège at the time of Victor Hugo” offers an itinerary based on Victor Hugo’s visits in 1840 and 1864 which will give you the chance to experience a 19th century in process of industrial and urban transformation.
\n\n
The first itinerary about Victor Hugo is the result of a cooperation with the City of Liège. We intend developing new itineraries. If you have any exciting ideas, do let us know.
\n\n
“Lost in Liège” : probably the only polymorphous guide created by locals about the city of Liège.“Lost in Liège” offers you an itinerary available in three complementary media: (1) paper map and brochure that you can download and print, (2) a website – www.lostinliege.com and (3) a smartphone application for Android and iPhone that you can download.
\n\n
Why the project? Simply because we love Liège, enjoy discovering our city and showing it to others. This discovery includes places and anecdotes that are not mentioned in other “conventional” guides. We want you to have pleasant discoveries and make your visit more interesting. Our idea is to take the visitor by the hand as if they were a friend visiting from abroad and show them around our city. Hence, the “Lost in Liège” project was born.</string>

</resources>